freewarezoom.com 2014-04-24

# Privacy - Freeware Download List

**Freewarezoom Privacy Statement**  
What follows is the Privacy Statement for all Freewarezoom websites including all the websites run under the www.Freewarezoom.com domain.

Please read this statement regarding our website. If you have questions please ask us via our [contact form](http://freewarezoom.com/contact/).

 **Ownership of Information**  
Freewarezoom is the sole owner of any information collected on our websites.

 **Comments/Message Boards**  
Most Freewarezoom websites contain comment sections. We do not actively monitor these comments and the information on them is for entertainment purposes only. If we are alerted to something we deem inappropriate in any way, we may delete it at our discretion. We use email validation on most of our comment sections in order to reduce “comment spam.” These email addresses will not be shared with any third party.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.Freewarezoom.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.Freewarezoom.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.Freewarezoom.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.Freewarezoom.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

 **Traffic Reports**  
Our industry-standard traffic reporting records IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded. We use this information in the aggregate only to provide traffic statistics to advertisers and to figure out which features and editorials are most popular.

 **Legal proceedings**  
We will make every effort to preserve user privacy but Freewarezoom may need to disclose information when required by law.

 **Business Transitions**  
If Freewarezoom is acquired by or merges with another firm, the assets of our websites, including personal information, will likely be transferred to the new firm.

 **Links**  
Freewarezoom websites frequently link to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our websites we encourage you to read the destination site’s privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Freewarezoom

 **Notification of Changes**  
When Freewarezoom makes changes to this privacy policy we will post those changes here.

 **Contact Information**  
If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please [contact us](http://freewarezoom.com/contact/).
